Guide to the R.R. Donnelley & Sons Company Archive 1844-2005
University of Chicago Library
- Series IX. General Records
  - Subseries 1: General Records
    - Financial printing, Donnelley SEC Proxy Rules Handbook, Jan. 1984 (Box 457, Folder 2)
    - Financial printing, Donnelley SEC Foreign Issuer Forms, Jan. 1985 (Box 457, Folder 3)
    - Financial printing, Donnelley SEC Handbook, 1984 (Box 457, Folder 4)
    - Financial printing, Donnelley SEC Handbook, Jan. 1985 (Box 458, Folder 1-2)
    - Financial printing, SEC Handbook, 1988-1989 (Box 458, Folder 3)
    - Foil printing, Aluminum Company of America (ALCOA), printing agreement, Sept 1, 1960 (Box 459, Folder 1)
    - Foil printing, Proposal to ALCOA, June 12, 1960 (Box 459, Folder 2)
    - Foil printing, ALCOA, 1959-1964 (Box 459, Folder 3-9)
    - Four American Books, preliminary study, 1929 (Box 460, Folder 1)
    - Four American Books, prospectus (Box 460, Folder 2)
    - Four American Books, sample pages from books for tipping in to prospectus (Box 460, Folder 3)
    - Four American Books, Herbert P. Zimmerman, "Story of The Four American Books," 1952 (Box 460, Folder 4-5)
    - Four American Books, proofs for Walden (Box 460, Folder 6)
    - Four American Books, "The Christening of Moby Dick," invitation (Box 460, Folder 7)
    - Four American Books, Herbert P. Zimmerman, "Story of the Moby Dick Trade Edition," 1952 (Box 460, Folder 8)
    - Four American Books, Moby Dick trade edition prospectus (Box 461, Folder 1)
    - Four American Books, Moby Dick, selected photographs and negatives of illustrations (Box 461, Folder 2)
    - Four American Books, Moby Dick, wrapping paper (Box 461, Folder 3)
    - Four American Books, Contemporary American Book Illustration exhibition catalog, 1930 (Box 461, Folder 4)
    - Four American Books, "Rockwell Kent and His Publishers," brochure, 1931 (Box 461, Folder 5)
    - Four American Books, Newberry Library, "A Checklist of Editions of Moby Dick 1851-1976" (Box 461, Folder 6)
    - Four American Books, Library of America, evening at the Newberry Library in celebration of Moby Dick, 1983 (Box 461, Folder 7)
    - Four American Books, Moby Dick United States postal stamp (Box 461, Folder 8)
    - Four American Books, Moby Dick, A Picture Voyage, 2002 (Box 461, Folder 9)
    - Four American Books, Distant Shores, The Odyssey of Rockwell Kent, Terra Museum of American Art exhibition, 2000 (Box 461, Folder 10)
    - Four American Books, Rudolph Ruzicka to Herbert P. Zimmerman, correspondence regarding Boston Public Library use of illustrations from Walden, 1951 (Box 461, Folder 11)
    - Four American Books, Three American Books prospectus (Box 461, Folder 12)
    - Four American Books, sales records (Box 461, Folder 13)
    - Four American Books, requests to use illustrations (Box 462, Folder 1)
    - Four American Books, rights to illustrations statement (Box 462, Folder 2)
    - Four American Books, Two Years before the Mast illustration reprint request by The Heritage Press, correspondence, 1946-1949 (Box 462, Folder 3)
    - Four American Books, H.P. Zimmerman, Rudolph Ruzicka and Frantize Laichter correspondence regarding Czech edition of Walden, 1948-1950 (Box 462, Folder 4)
    - Four American Books, post-publication information (Box 462, Folder 5)
    - Four American Books, copyright correspondence, Random House (Box 462, Folder 6)
    - Four American Books, copyright correspondence (Box 462, Folder 7)
    - Four American Books, Three American Books prospectus (Box 462, Folder 8)
    - Four American Books, Claire Badaracco, American Culture and the Market Place, RR Donnelley's Four American Books Campaign, 1926-1930, 1992 (Box 462, Folder 9)
    - Four American Books, Caxtonian, 1994 (Box 462, Folder 10)
    - Four American Books, Shedd Aquarium, use of illustration from Moby Dick, 1994 (Box 462, Folder 11)
    - Four American Books, Grolier Club, Rockwell Kent, Selections from the Stanley Collection, 1997 (Box 462, Folder 12)
    - Four American Books, Library of America, "Dimensions of Moby Dick," undated (Box 463, Folder 1)
    - Great Chicago Fire, offprint from Donnelley Printer (Box 463, Folder 2)
    - Great Chicago Fire, "Chicago, City on Fire," Commerce magazine, 1971 (Box 463, Folder 3)
    - Great Chicago Fire, Leroy Church memoir, 1871-1952 (Box 463, Folder 4)
    - Great Chicago Fire, newspaper clipping regarding destruction and rebuilding of Lakeside Press building, ca. 1872 (Box 463, Folder 5)
    - Holiday Press, general (Box 463, Folder 6)
    - Holiday Press, ADV, 1927, 1st book published, two copies (Box 463, Folder 7)
    - Holiday Press, A Lincoln and Whitman Miscellany, broadside, 1938 (Box 463, Folder 8)
    - Holiday Press, Notes and Reminiscences, George Ade and John T. McCutcheon, photographs of Ade and other Holiday Press members at a golf outing and luncheon at Ade's home, 1941 (Box 463, Folder 9)
    - Holiday Press, Voyages to Vinland, photographs, 1941 (Box 463, Folder 10)
    - Holiday Press, promotional brochure, June 1942 (Box 463, Folder 11)
    - Holiday Press, stationery (Box 463, Folder 12)
    - Holiday Press, Eric Gill alphabet broadside, 1942 (Box 463, Folder 13)
    - Holiday Press, Voyages to Vinland, 1941 (Box 463, Folder 14)
    - Holiday Press, A Lincoln and Whitman Miscellany, 1938 (Box 463, Folder 15)
    - Holiday Press, Harry J. Owens, The Scandalous Adventures of Reynard the Fox, 1945 (Box 464, Folder 1)
    - Holiday Press, Harry J. Owens, The Scandalous Adventures of Reynard the Fox, signatures, ca. 1945 (Box 464, Folder 2)
    - Holiday Press, Notes and Reminiscences, George Ade and John T. McCutcheon, 1940 (Box 464, Folder 3)
    - Indian head printer's mark, general (Box 464, Folder 4)
    - Indian head printer's mark, J.C. Leyendecker design, 1897 (Box 464, Folder 5)
    - Indian head printer's mark, Ignatz Sahula design, 1923 (Box 464, Folder 6)
    - Indian head printer's mark, Theodore Hapgood design, 1926 (Box 464, Folder 7)
    - Indian head printer's mark, Rockwell Kent design, 1933 (Box 464, Folder 8)
    - Indian head printer's mark, Joseph Carter design, 1953 (Box 464, Folder 9)
    - Indian head printer's mark, Stanislawa Nowicki design, 1950s (Box 465, Folder 1)
    - Indian head printer's mark, Curtis Hill design, 1968 (Box 465, Folder 2)
    - Indian head printer's mark, Mobium design, 1981 (Box 465, Folder 3)
    - Indian head printer's mark, Mobium design, 1992 (Box 465, Folder 4)
    - Indian head printer's mark, Lakeside News articles (Box 465, Folder 5)
    - Indian head printer's mark, use in advertising pieces (Box 465, Folder 6)
    - Indian head printer's mark, holiday card featuring variety of designs, 1981 (Box 465, Folder 7)
    - Indian head printer's mark, Training School logo (Box 465, Folder 8)
    - Indian head printer's mark, alternate and unused versions (Box 465, Folder 9)
    - Indian head printer's mark, slides (Box 465, Folder 10)
    - Indian head printer's mark, examples of use (Box 465, Folder 11)
    - Indian head printer's mark, Lakeside Classic logo (Box 465, Folder 12)
    - Indian head printer's mark, proofs, photographs and artwork (Box 465, Folder 13-15)
    - Indian head printer's mark, scrapbook pages with samples, correspondence and artwork (Box 466, Folder 1)
    - Indian head printer's mark, files of proofs and photographs (Box 466, Folder 2-4)
    - Labels and wraps, general (Box 466, Folder 5)
    - Labels and wraps, James Elmo Smith, improved protractor scale cards, 1912 (Box 466, Folder 6)
    - Labels and wraps, Chandler Montgomery agreement to investigate child's table and chair production, 1934 (Box 466, Folder 7)
    - Labels and wraps, wall paper market, 1972 (Box 466, Folder 8)
    - Labels and wraps, Camel Cigarette wrappers, 1966 (Box 466, Folder 9)
    - Labels and wraps, Campbell's Soup labels, 1969 (Box 466, Folder 10)
    - Labels and wraps, mailing and product labels (Box 466, Folder 11)
    - Labels and wraps, samples from roll sheeter press, used to print cereal box wrappers, ca. 1970 (Box 466, Folder 12)
    - Labels and wraps, letterpress labels (Box 466, Folder 13)
    - Lakeside Annual Directory, "Donnelley's National Classified Telephone Directory," Lakeside Press, 1917 (Box 467, Folder 1)
    - Lakeside Annual Directory, articles (Box 467, Folder 2)
    - Lakeside Annual Directory, notes on production costs, 1908-1910 (Box 467, Folder 3)
    - Lakeside Annual Directory, composition proposal from Brown- Cooper Typesetting Company, 1905 (Box 467, Folder 4)
    - Lakeside Annual Directory, original front binding board, undated (Box 467, Folder 5)
    - Lakeside Annual Directory, original title page and photograph, 1887 (Box 467, Folder 6)
    - Lakeside Annual Directory, photocopies of selected pages, 1880 (Box 467, Folder 7)
    - Lakeside Annual Directory, photocopies of selected pages, 1881 (Box 467, Folder 8)
    - Lakeside Annual Directory, photocopies of selected pages, 1883 (Box 467, Folder 9)
    - Lakeside Annual Directory, Chicago Directory, photocopies of selected pages 1884 (Box 467, Folder 10)
    - Lakeside Annual Directory, photocopies of selected pages, 1886 (Box 467, Folder 11)
    - Lakeside Annual Directory, The Lakeside City Directory, photocopies of selected pages, 1886 (Box 467, Folder 12)
    - Lakeside Annual Directory, The Lakeside City Directory, photocopies of selected pages, 1887 (Box 467, Folder 13)
    - Lakeside Annual Directory, map of Chicago, photocopies of selected pages, 1887 (Box 467, Folder 14)
    - Lakeside Annual Directory, photocopies of selected pages, 1887 (Box 467, Folder 15)
    - Lakeside Annual Directory, Chicago Telephone Directory, photocopies of selected pages, 1901 (Box 467, Folder 16)
    - Lakeside Annual Directory, St. Louis Telephone Directory, photocopies of selected pages, 1927 (Box 467, Folder 17)
    - Lakeside Bank, general (Box 468, Folder 1)
    - Lakeside Bank, presentation of charter, photograph, 1965 (Box 468, Folder 2)
    - Lakeside Bank, article on opening in Donnelley Printer, fall 1966 (Box 468, Folder 3)
    - Lakeside Bank, statement of services, 1966 (Box 468, Folder 4)
    - Lakeside Bank, first prospectus, 1966 (Box 468, Folder 5)
    - Lakeside Bank, renewal of Chicago's south side, exhibition, photographs, 1967 (Box 468, Folder 6)
    - Lakeside Bank, annual report, 1975 (Box 468, Folder 7)
    - Lakeside Bank, annual report, 1972 (Box 468, Folder 8)
    - Lakeside Bank, John R. Montgomery III, President, photographs (Box 468, Folder 9)
    - Lakeside Bank, grand opening, photographs, April 29, 1965 (Box 468, Folder 10)
    - Lakeside Bank, architect's drawing, photograph (Box 468, Folder 11)
    - Lakeside Bank, construction photograph, 1966 (Box 468, Folder 12)
    - Lakeside Bank, building condemned, 1991 (Box 468, Folder 13)
    - Lakeside Bank, opening of nranch office at 55 West Wacker, 1991 (Box 468, Folder 14)
    - Lakeside Bank, ribbon and dollar bill from opening event at 55 West Wacker Branch, 1991 (Box 468, Folder 15)
    - Lakeside Classics, T.E. Donnelley, correspondence, 1938-1946 (Box 468, Folder 16-17)
    - Lakeside Classics, T.E. Donnelley, correspondence, 1943-1956 (Box 469, Folder 1-2)
    - Lakeside Classics, Life of Olaudah Equiano, 2004 (Box 469, Folder 3)
    - Lakeside Classics, master standard and list of recipients, 1992 (Box 469, Folder 4-5)
    - Lakeside Cookbook, general (Box 469, Folder 6)
    - Lakeside Library, list of titles (Box 469, Folder 7)
    - Lakeside Library, research compiled from individual issues, 1961 (Box 469, Folder 8)
    - Lakeside Library, inventory of issues held by RR Donnelley, undated (Box 469, Folder 9)
    - Lakeside Library, correspondence with researchers, ca. 1943 (Box 469, Folder 10)
    - Lakeside Library, Lydia Cushman Schurman, "The Social, Economic and Literary History of Book, Newspaper and Magazine Publishing," Publishing History, 1996 (Box 469, Folder 11)
    - Lakeside Library, Raymond Shove, Cheap Book Production in the U.S. 1870-1891, 1931 (Box 470, Folder 1)
    - Lakeside Library, photocopies of selected material (Box 470, Folder 2-3)
    - Lakeside Library, The Weekly Lakeside and The American Library, photocopies of selected material (Box 470, Folder 4)
    - Lakeside Library, The Western Monthly, photocopies of selected material (Box 470, Folder 5)
    - Lakeside Library, The Lakeside Monthly, photocopies of selected material (Box 470, Folder 6)
    - Lakeside Library, The Weekly Lakeside, and The American Library, photocopies of selected material, 1882-1883 (Box 470, Folder 7)
    - Lakeside Press Mutual Savings Association, 1924 (Box 470, Folder 8)
    - Limited Editions Club, newsletters, 1929-1933 (Box 470, Folder 9)
    - Limited Editions Club, newsletters, 1933-1939 (Box 471, Folder 1)
    - Limited Editions Club, announcements (Box 471, Folder 2)
    - Limited Editions Club, special printings, articles and dedication of George Macy Memorial Collection (Box 471, Folder 3)
    - Limited Editions Club, prospectuses, 1931-1938 (Box 471, Folder 4)
    - Limited Editions Club, catalogs (Box 471, Folder 5)
    - Madonna, printing controversy, 1992 (Box 471, Folder 6)
    - Magazines, general (Box 471, Folder 7-8)
    - Magazines, insert samples, 1981-1992 (Box 472, Folder 1-4)
    - Memorial Library, Donnelley Printer feature article, Winter 1965 (Box 472, Folder 5)
    - Memorial Library, articles (Box 472, Folder 6)
    - Memorial Library, Richard Archer, Lakeside News article, 1957 (Box 472, Folder 7)
    - Memorial Library, standard practices and collection development policies (Box 473, Folder 1)
    - Memorial Library, "Practices and Procedures for R.R. Donnelley Libraries," 1965 (Box 473, Folder 2)
    - Memorial Library, check-out card (Box 473, Folder 3)
    - Memorial Library, shelf arrangement (Box 473, Folder 4)
    - Memorial Library, conservation and preservation records, Memorial Library collections, 1950s-1970s (Box 473, Folder 5)
    - Memorial Library, Maintenance and environmental control (Box 473, Folder 6)
    - Memorial Library, Charles Z. Klauder, architect (Box 473, Folder 7)
    - Memorial Library, brochure (Box 473, Folder 8)
    - Memorial Library, description (Box 473, Folder 9)
    - Memorial Library, details of wood, windows, furniture and other decorative elements (Box 473, Folder 10)
    - Memorial Library, diagram of shelving (Box 473, Folder 11)
    - Memorial Library, books in foreign languages (Box 473, Folder 12)
    - Memorial Library, acquisition correspondence (Box 473, Folder 13)
    - Memorial Library, RR Donnelley printed books purchased from Mrs. Gordon, 1946 (Box 473, Folder 14)
    - Memorial Library, monthly activities reports, Jan. 1964-Nov. 1966 (Box 473, Folder 15)
    - Memorial Library, circulation statistics, 1966-1976 (Box 473, Folder 16)
    - Memorial Library, librarian job description (Box 473, Folder 17)
    - Memorial Library, bookplates (Box 473, Folder 18)
    - Memorial Library, reorganization, 1966 (Box 473, Folder 19)
    - Memorial Library, stock catalogs in collection, 1965 (Box 473, Folder 20)
    - Memorial Library, collection inventories (Box 473, Folder 1)
    - Memorial Library, 1st floor inventory, May 1973 (Box 473, Folder 2)
    - Memorial Library, 2nd floor inventory, May 1973 (Box 473, Folder 3)
    - Memorial Library, list of early RR Donnelley print material in collection, 1864-1908, compiled 1961 (Box 473, Folder 4)
    - Memorial Library, periodic disposal lists (Box 473, Folder 5)
    - Memorial Library, Stone & Kimball imprints, purchase receipts, 1951 (Box 473, Folder 6)
    - Memorial Library, unidentified list of books (Box 473, Folder 7)
    - Newberry Library, inventory of gift of materials from RR Donnelley, 1997 (Box 475, Folder 1)
    - Newberry Library, gift of books from RR Donnelley, 1995 (Box 475, Folder 2)
    - Newsletters, First Person, 1995-1999 (Box 475, Folder 3)
    - Newsletters, Business Brief, 2003 (Box 475, Folder 4)
    - Newsletters, E2E Solutions, 2001 (Box 475, Folder 5)
    - Newsletters, Reno Impressions, 2003 (Box 475, Folder 6)
    - Newsletters, Innovation by R.R. Donnelley, 2001-2002 (Box 475, Folder 7)
    - Newsletters, Donnelley Owners Business Brief, 1997 (Box 475, Folder 8)
    - Newsletters, Hi-Lites, 2002-2003 (Box 475, Folder 9)
    - Newsletters, Print, Stitch and Trim Journal, 2002-2003 (Box 475, Folder 10)
    - Newsletters, Crusader, 1995 (Box 475, Folder 11)
    - Newsletters, Corporate Center Press, 1997-1999 (Box 475, Folder 12)
    - Newsletters, Gallatin's Signature, 2002 (Box 475, Folder 13)
    - Preliminary and pre-press processes (Box 475, Folder 14)
    - Preliminary and pre-press processes, "The Teletype Story," 1966 (Box 476, Folder 1)
    - Preliminary and pre-press processes, offset preliminary committee meeting with Charles W. Lake, 1970 (Box 476, Folder 2)
    - Preliminary and pre-press processes, Photocomp layout, 1980s (Box 476, Folder 3)
    - Preliminary and pre-press processes, digital filmless pre-press, ca. 1985-1986 (Box 476, Folder 4-5)
    - Preliminary and pre-press processes, Pulsar merchandiser's publishing system, brochure, 1980s (Box 476, Folder 6)
    - Preliminary and pre-press processes, digital technology, 1990s (Box 476, Folder 7)
    - Printers' marks, general (Box 476, Folder 8-9)
    - Printers' marks, publications and guides, ca. 1930s-1940s (Box 476, Folder 10)
    - Printing history, articles on the readability of type (Box 477, Folder 1)
    - Printing history, "The Invention of Printing," American Institute of Graphic Arts, booklet, 1940 (Box 477, Folder 2)
    - Printing history, William Caxton (Box 477, Folder 3)
    - Printing history, Benjamin Franklin (Box 477, Folder 4-6)
    - Printing history, Gutenberg (Box 477, Folder 7)
    - Printing history, exhibitions at the Smithsonian, photographs, ca. 1930 (Box 477, Folder 8)
    - Printing history, Ramage Press, 1844 (Box 477, Folder 9)
    - Printing history, Douglas C. McMurtrie, "The Price of Printing in Philadelphia, 1754," 1928 (Box 477, Folder 10)
    - Printing history, Frank M. Sherman, "The Genesis of Machine Typesetting," 1950 (Box 477, Folder 11)
    - Printing history, "Very Truly Yours, Monotype System," Typographic Services Company, booklet, 1936 (Box 477, Folder 12)
    - Printing history, George J. Mills, "Paper Cutting, Machines and Techniques," 1949 (Box 477, Folder 13)
    - Printing history, Douglas C. McMurtrie, "Type Design in the United States," 1924 (Box 477, Folder 14)
    - Printing history, Edward G. Gress, "Typographic Styles Change Every Generation," 1930 (Box 477, Folder 15)
    - Printing history, "Historical Sidelights," Lakeside News, 1949 (Box 477, Folder 16)
    - Printing paper and ink, paper, general (Box 477, Folder 17)
    - Printing paper and ink, T.E. Donnelley, "The American Decimal Standard of Weights for Paper," report for War Industries Board, ca. 1918 (Box 477, Folder 18)
    - Printing paper and ink, "Lakeside Press Unit System of Weights of Paper," chart, ca. 1925 (Box 477, Folder 19)
    - Printing paper and ink, Charles Crawford Whinery, article on paper, 1954 (Box 477, Folder 20)
    - Printing paper and ink, E.A. Gustafson, "Progress in the Paper Industry," 1960 (Box 477, Folder 21)
    - Printing paper and ink, summary of paper tonnage handled, 1973 (Box 477, Folder 22)
    - Printing paper and ink, ink, general (Box 477, Folder 23-25)
    - Printing paper and ink, Printing Ink Handbook, National Printing Ink Research Institute, 1967 (Box 478, Folder 1)
    - Printing paper and ink, ink manufacturing policy, 1968 (Box 478, Folder 2)
    - Printing paper and ink, ink developments, 1971 (Box 478, Folder 3)
    - Printing paper and ink, pollution-free ink, 1971 (Box 478, Folder 4)
    - Printing paper and ink, "Gravure Ink, to Make or Buy," report, 1973 (Box 478, Folder 5)
    - Printing paper and ink, correspondence with ink manufacturing companies, 1969-1980 (Box 478, Folder 6)
    - Printing presses, general (Box 478, Folder 7)
    - Printing presses, general, history of Chicago Tribune news presses, 1941 (Box 478, Folder 8)
    - Printing presses, general, J.B. Gill, "Web Press Standard Data," report, 1990 (Box 478, Folder 9)
    - Printing presses, general, 3-man crew 5/0 7/0 Miehle press investigation, 1945 (Box 478, Folder 10)
    - Printing presses, general, Goss presses (Box 479, Folder 1)
    - Printing presses, general, Harris presses (Box 479, Folder 2)
    - Printing presses, general, Toshiba presses (Box 479, Folder 3)
    - Printing presses, general, Miehle presses (Box 479, Folder 4)
    - Printing presses, general, Hoe presses, photographs (Box 479, Folder 5)
    - Printing presses, RR Donnelley presses by department and, number, ca. 1900-1970 Life 2/C presses 52-58 (Box 479, Folder 6)
    - Printing presses, RR Donnelley presses by department and, number, ca. 1900-1970 Department A, Chicago Department B, Chicago (Box 479, Folder 6)
    - Printing presses, RR Donnelley presses by department and, number, ca. 1900-1970 Department C, Chicago (Box 479, Folder 7-9)
    - Printing presses, RR Donnelley presses by department and, number, ca. 1900-1970 Department C, Chicago Department D, Chicago (Box 480, Folder 1)
    - Printing presses, RR Donnelley presses by department and, number, ca. 1900-1970 Department D, Chicago (Box 480, Folder 2-4)
    - Printing presses, RR Donnelley presses by department and, number, ca. 1900-1970 Department D, Chicago Department ED, Old Saybrook Department KM, Glasgow Department LM, Lancaster Department LTD, Lancaster West (Box 481, Folder 1)
    - Printing presses, RR Donnelley presses by department and, number, ca. 1900-1970 Department M, Chicago Department MC, Mattoon Department MR, Mattoon (Box 481, Folder 2)
    - Printing presses, RR Donnelley presses by department and, number, ca. 1900-1970 Department NC, North Plant, Chicago Department OTM, Willard Department OWM, Willard Department P, Glasgow (Box 481, Folder 3)
    - Printing presses, RR Donnelley presses by department and, number, ca. 1900-1970 Department R, Chicago Department RO, Chicago (Box 481, Folder 4)
    - Printing presses, RR Donnelley presses by department and, number, ca. 1900-1970 Department SC, South Plant, Chicago Department SD, South Plant, Chicago Department SX, South Plant, Chicago (Box 481, Folder 5)
    - Printing presses, RR Donnelley presses by department and, number, ca. 1900-1970 Department TR, Gallatin Department WR, Warsaw (Box 482, Folder 1)
    - Printing presses, RR Donnelley presses by department and, number, ca. 1900-1970 Department WRO, Warsaw Department Y, Chicago (Box 482, Folder 2)
    - Printing processes, general (Box 482, Folder 3)
    - Printing processes, gravure (Box 482, Folder 4)
    - Printing processes, offset (Box 482, Folder 5)
    - Printing processes, sheet fed and rotogravure, 1929 (Box 482, Folder 6)
    - Printing processes, Photo-Fact, 1930s (Box 483, Folder 1)
    - Printing processes, planography, 1933 (Box 483, Folder 2)
    - Printing processes, heat-set printing, 1936 (Box 483, Folder 3)
    - Printing processes, Win Isom, history of rotogravure, 1950 (Box 483, Folder 4)
    - Printing processes, Xography, 3-D printing, 1960s (Box 483, Folder 5)
    - Printing processes, Electrotyping printing practices manual, 1961 (Box 483, Folder 6)
    - Printing processes, engineering, research and development report on gravure preliminary requiring negatives and positives, 1961 (Box 483, Folder 7)
    - Printing processes, gravure printing samples, 1963 (Box 483, Folder 8)
    - Printing processes, Look-Kromatic, 1964 (Box 483, Folder 9)
    - Printing processes, Versacolor, 1967 (Box 483, Folder 10)
    - Printing processes, rotogravure sample booklet, 1986-1987 (Box 483, Folder 11)
    - Printing processes, letterpress (Box 483, Folder 12)
    - Printing processes, Nyloprint (Box 483, Folder 13)